<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

	<!-- General strings -->
	<string name="app_name">HPG Workout Tool</string>
	<string name="ok">ok</string>
	<string name="yes">yes</string>
	<string name="no">no</string>
	<string name="cancel">cancel</string>
	<string name="back">back</string>
	<string name="loading_str">loading...</string>
	<string name="saving_str">saving...</string>
	<string name="question_mark">\?</string>
	<string name="done">done</string>
		<string name="done_title">Done</string>
	<string name="decimal_point">.</string>
	<string name="clear">C</string>
	<string name="hpg_logo_desc">Logo for the Hyde Park Gym</string>


	<!-- WARNING:
		This string must match EXACTLY with the item in the
		exercise list that the user select to enter a custom
		item.
		If this changes, then you much change all the arrays
		in arrays.xml to match this.  And vice versa.
	-->
	<string name="custom_item_name">custom</string>

	<!-- General Help Titles and Messages -->
	<string name="cancel_title">Cancel</string>
	<string name="none_selected">none selected</string>
	<string name="select">select</string>
	<string name="unit">unit</string>
	<string name="unit_label">Unit</string>
	<string name="name">name</string>

	<!-- Universal Menu Buttons -->
	<string name="menu_help_button">help</string>
	<string name="menu_zoomin_button">\ grow text</string>
	<string name="menu_zoomout_button">\ shrink it</string>
	<string name="menu_zoomreset_button">reset text</string>

	<!-- ============          			============ -->
	<!-- ============ Multiple Activity  ============ -->
	<!-- ============          			============ -->

	<string name="label_reps">reps = %s</string>
	<string name="label_weight">weight (%1$s) = %2$s</string>
	<string name="label_level">level = %s</string>
	<string name="label_cals">cals = %s</string>
	<string name="label_dist">distance (%1$s) = %2$s</string>
	<string name="label_time">time (%1$s) = %2$s</string>
	<string name="label_other">%1$s (%2$s) = %3$s</string>


	<!-- ============		 ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Welcome ============ -->
	<!-- ============		 ============ -->
	<string name="welcome_title">Hyde Park Gym</string>
	<string name="welcome_subtitle">Workout Tool</string>

	<string name="welcome_start_button">workout</string>
	<string name="welcome_start_help_title">start a workout</string>
	<string name="welcome_start_help_msg">Press this button to
		begin or continue working out.
		\n\nThis takes you to the Grid, where all your exercises
		are listed and the details of your workouts can be
		found.
		\n\nHave fun!</string>

	<string name="welcome_settings_button">preferences</string>
	<string name="welcome_settings_help_title">Preferences</string>
	<string name="welcome_settings_help_msg">Tap on this
		button to change the settings for this program.
		\n\nDon\'t worry, they are pretty straight-forward.</string>

	<string name="welcome_export_button">import/export</string>
	<string name="welcome_export_help_title">Export Your Workout</string>
	<string name="welcome_export_help_msg">
		This button takes you to a screen where you may
		export your workout to some common formats.
		\n\n(Right now, this part is still a work-in-progress,
		so it doesn\'t do much.)
	</string>

	<string name="welcome_graphs_button">look at graphs</string>
	<string name="welcome_graphs_help_title">Graph Progress</string>
	<string name="welcome_graphs_help_msg">Seeing your progress
		is a great part of getting in shape. Press this button
		to look at all sorts of graphs of how your workouts and
		your body is changing over time.</string>

	<string name="welcome_exit_button">exit</string>
	<string name="welcome_exit_help_title">Exit Program</string>
	<string name="welcome_exit_help_msg">Press this button
		to quit the application. Surprised\? Didn\'t think
		so.</string>

	<string name="welcome_help_help_title">Help!</string>
	<string name="welcome_help_help_msg">Welcome to the
		Hyde Park Gym Workout Tool. This app keeps track of
		your workouts and tracks your progress.
		\n\nThis app is descriptive, not proscriptive.  That is, it does
		not tell
		you what you SHOULD do, it just keeps track of what you did.
		I think
		you are smart enough to know what sort of workout you want (or
		at least to find the information for yourself).
		\n\nFor general help about what a screen does, tap on
		the Hyde Park Gym logo at the top right of the screen.
		\n\nFor help on specific functions, press and hold
		any button or widget, and a help message will pop up
		describing that function.
		\n\nThe first
		time you use this app, a few popular exercises are
		listed already listed. You will have to add your favorite
		exercises to the list. But the
		program will remember your exercises, so the next
		time you workout, you can simply select that
		exercise from the list.
		\n\nChoose an exercise and record how
		much you completed for that set. Do it again for each
		set. The data you
		enter is added to a database which can be viewed
		to track your progress.
		\n\nThis app was created by Scott Morgan Biggs in his spare
		time. The good people at Hyde Park Gym provided invaluable help
		and assistance. They also trusted me with their good name, but
		are in no way responsible for any damage, frustration, or insults
		that may (or may not) crop up while using this app.  So you should
		send your hate messages to me through the Google Play site. I promise
		to do my best to address the issues (which may not be much--I am
		very far from a programming god, sorry). Anyway, I did lots of
		this stuff in the middle of the night, so you might be amused or
		offended by some of these help messages. So it goes. But in any
		event, I hope this app is as useful to you as it has been to me
		and the people at HPG.
		\n\nHave a good workout!</string>

	<string name="welcome_menu_credits_button">show credits</string>
	<string name="welcome_menu_credits_title">Show Credits</string>
	<string name="welcome_menu_credits_msg">Hyde Park Gym is owned
		and run by Brook Jones. This tool was created with the
		help of him and many of the other fine folks at Hyde Park
		Gym in Austin, Texas--just look for place with the arm
		sticking out! Programmed by Scott Biggs.</string>
	<string name="welcome_menu_exit_button">exit</string>

	<!-- ============	 ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Add ============ -->
	<!-- ============	 ============ -->
	<!-- Note:  lots of these are also used by the Edit screen -->

	<!-- The dialog that pops up when they hit the Back button -->
	<string name="addexer_leave_title">Really\?</string>
	<string name="addexer_leave_msg">Are you sure you want to
		go back to the main workout screen\? This will abandon
		all entries you\'ve made here.</string>

	<!-- Menus -->
	<string name="addexer_help_title">Add Exercise Help</string>
	<string name="addexer_help_msg">On this screen you create
		a new exercise for your workout list.
		\n\nGive
		this exercise a good name (something to easily distinguish
		it from other exercises). Like all things here, if you
		change your mind later, you can easily come back and edit
		the name.
		\n\nExercises generally fall into two different types: anaerobic
		and aerobic. Anaerobic are strength building exercises like
		bench presses and squats. Aerobic exercises build endurance
		and cardiovascular health (jogging, jump rope, and swimming
		for examples). You need to tell this program what type of
		exercise this is because it does keep track, and we don\'t
		want to confuse how your muscles are worked!
		\n\nAlso, this program wants to know which group of muscles
		you are using with this exercise. You don\'t have to be
		too specific; a rough guesstimate is good enough.
		\n\nSelect the
		checkbox to left for each measurement you want to record
		for this exercise. Uncheck to disable this measurement.
		\n\nThen touch the drop-down to the right to select the unit
		of measurement.  If you want to create your own unit,
		select \'customize\' and fill in the following form.
		\n\nFor each exercise, there is usually one measurement that
		is the most important. Select the radio button on the right
		side next to the measurement that is the most important
		part of this particular exercise.
		\n\nThe \'other\' section allows you to completely customize.
		You can name both the measurement AND the unit. This is
		for those exercises that I just could not think of.
		\n\nAnd like always, you can long-touch (touch and hold for
		two seconds) any widget and get specific help for that
		item.
		\n\nNow for an example:\n
		A good friend is a competitive synchronized swimmer, and her
		group has some unusual types of exercises for their team.
		\n\nOne of them is called \'Smiling\', so she enters that
		for the name of her exercise.
		\n\nRepetitions are important for this one, so she checks \'reps\'.
		\n\nThere are no levels to this exercise, so she leaves this
		unchecked (levels are generally used with exercise machines
		like Stair Steppers or rowers).
		\n\nCalories? Yes, she is quite concerned about calories, but
		there is no simple way to measure them.  So this is left blank.
		\n\nSmiling is not weighted (imagine if it were!), so that remains unchecked.
		\n\nHowever there is a distance, so she checks \'distanced\'
		and taps on the drop-down button and selects \'millimeters\'.
		\n\nTime is measured for this exercise, so she checks \'timed\'.
		They do this exercise to music, counting beats.  But beats
		are not in the time list, so she chooses \'custom\' from
		the drop-down list and types \'beats\' in the editbox.
		\n\nBut there is one more aspect to the Smiling workout that
		the program has not provided for: glow. So my friend
		checks \'other\' and types \'glow\' in the textbox
		next to it.
		\n\nThe unit for glowing while smiling is called \'happies\', so
		she types this in the lower box.
		\n\nLastly, she must decide which of these is the most significant
		part of the smiling exercise. While glowing is very important, this
		is an exercise, and she most wants to keep track of the repetitions.
		So she selects the right-most radio button in the \'reps\' row.
		\n\nLike other programs you have used, hit \'ok\' to save the
		changes, and \'cancel\' if you change your mind and like
		things the way they were.
		\n\nRemember, if you later decide to change anything, you can
		edit an exercise by long-pressing it in the main \'grid\'.
		\n\nYeah, that\'s a long explanation. But you deserve to
		really understand what you\'re doing. Right\? Have
		a great workout!
	</string>

	<string name="addexer_cancel_warning_title">Cancel Add Exercise</string>
	<string name="addexer_cancel_warning_msg">It looks like you
		are about to cancel, even though you\'ve done a little
		work on this new exercise.
		\n\nAre you sure you want to cancel\?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>


	<!-- The Widgets -->

	<!-- For the title at the top of the screen. -->
	<string name="addexer_title_add_msg">Add a New Exercise</string>

	<!-- The TextView label preceeds name edittext widget. -->
	<string name="addexer_name_label">new name</string>
	<string name="addexer_name_hint">exercise name</string>

	<!-- These are for the AlertDialog that comes up as a ContextMenu -->
	<string name="addexer_name_help_title">Exercise Name</string>
	<string name="addexer_name_help_msg">Type in the name of
		this exercise here.</string>

	<!-- The Toast that complains that this was not filled out correctly. -->
	<string name="addexer_name_complaint">Please enter an exercise name.</string>

	<!-- The Type label and spinner -->
	<string name="addexer_type_label">exercise type</string>
	<string name="addexer_type_help_title">Exercise Type</string>
	<string name="addexer_type_help_msg">Exercises work your
		body in different ways. Aerobic workouts are for
		endurance. Anaerobic workouts increase strength.
		Some exercises do both, and others just can\'t
		be categorized. Do your best to pick the most
		appropriate type for this workout.</string>
	<string name="addexer_type_complaint">Please select an
		exercise type.</string>

	<!-- For the title -->
	<string name="addexer_type_str">What type of exercise\?</string>

	<!-- For the Muscle Group -->
	<string name="addexer_musclegroup_label">muscle group</string>
	<string name="addexer_musclegroup_str">Which group of muscles\?</string>
	<string name="addexer_musclegroup_help_title">Muscle Group</string>
	<string name="addexer_musclegroup_help_msg">Tell this program
		which muscle group this exercise targets. Information here
		will help the program keep track of what muscles you are
		exercising and will give more accurate progress charts.</string>
	<string name="addexer_musclegroup_complaint">Please select a
		muscle group.</string>

	<!-- For the title of the ListBox that holds the CheckBoxes -->
	<string name="addexer_checkbox_title">measurements</string>
	<string name="addexer_checkbox_significant">significant</string>
	<string name="addexer_checkbox_complaint">Please select at least
		one measurement.</string>

	<string name="addexer_unit_msg">Select in the unit of
		measurement you want to work with.
		\n\nIf you do not see what you need, feel free to
		select \'custom\' to create the unit you want to use.
		</string>


	<string name="addexer_rep_label">reps</string>
	<string name="addexer_rep_help_title">Repetitions</string>
	<string name="addexer_rep_help_msg">Select this checkbox ON
		(checked) if this exercise has multiple repetitions that
		you want to count. Push-ups will use this. Jogging probably
		will not (unless you obsessively count your steps!). If this
		is selected, the program will ask you how many time (reps)
		you performed this exercise.</string>

	<string name="addexer_weight_label">weighted</string>
	<string name="addexer_weight_help_title">Weighted Checkbox</string>
	<string name="addexer_weight_help_msg">Turn this checkbox
		ON (checked) if this workout uses weighted equipment.
		In other words, how much mass are you moving\?
		Otherwise this program won\'t bother asking you
		to enter a weight on this exercise.</string>
	<string name="addexer_weight_unit_title">Unit of Weight</string>
	<string name="addexer_weight_unit_msg">Type in the measurement
		unit you\'re working on. Some examples: pounds, kilograms,
		ounces, tons, stones, picograms, etc.</string>

	<string name="addexer_dist_label">distanced</string>
	<string name="addexer_dist_help_title">Distanced Checkbox</string>
	<string name="addexer_dist_help_msg">Turn this checkbox ON
		(checked) if this workout measures distance. Obviously
		you won\'t use this one for bench presses. But many aerobic
		exercises (like swimming) measure distances. If this is
		not checked the program won\'t bother asking you to enter
		any distances for this exercise.</string>
	<string name="addexer_dist_unit_title">Unit of Distance</string>
	<string name="addexer_dist_unit_msg">How far are you
		going\? But we need to know the unit. Any unit will
		do, like feet, kilometers, inches, milimeters,
		yards, parsecs, etc.</string>

	<string name="addexer_time_label">timed</string>
	<string name="addexer_time_help_title">Timed Checkbox</string>
	<string name="addexer_time_help_msg">Turn this checkbox ON
		(checked) if this workout measures time in any way (like
		how long the exercise takes, or even a race). Otherwise
		this program won\'t bother asking you to enter a time with
		this exercise.</string>
	<string name="addexer_time_unit_title">Unit of Time</string>
	<string name="addexer_time_unit_msg">What time unit do
		you measure this exercise with\? Type it in here.
		Try seconds, minutes, hours, days, centuries, or
		whatever fits this exercise.</string>

	<string name="addexer_level_label">levels</string>
	<string name="addexer_level_help_title">Levels Checkbox</string>
	<string name="addexer_level_help_msg">Turn this checkbox ON
		(checked) if this workout uses some sort of level.
		\n\nFor example, a stair climber may have a speed setting;
		you can use Levels to keep track of this speed. Otherwise
		this program won\'t bother asking you to enter any levels.
	</string>

	<string name="addexer_calorie_label">calories</string>
	<string name="addexer_calorie_help_title">Calories Checkbox</string>
	<string name="addexer_calorie_help_msg">Turn this checkbox ON
		(checked) if you want to count calories for this exercise!
		\n\nWhile this program does not calculate calories for you,
		many exercise machines do.  You can enter that information
		here and this app will keep track of it. Cool, right?
		Yeah yeah, I know--it\'s just a program.
	</string>

			<string name="addexer_other_label">other</string>
	<string name="addexer_other_complaint">Please fill out both text
		boxes for \'Other\'.</string>
		<string name="addexer_other_help_title">Other Measurement</string>
	<string name="addexer_other_help_msg">In the likely case
		that I forgot some sort of exercise measurement,
		checking this line should take care the problem.
		Of course, if you are satisfied with the regular
		measurements, you can ignore this section and
		leave it unchecked.
		\n\nThe name of the measurement and the unit are also
		needed. Later, when you perform this exercise,
		the app will use this name you typed and ask for the number
		of units you did for that set.
		\n\nFor example, when working out with tiddly-winks, I
		need to keep track of progessively larger sizes of
		my winks. So
		I\'ll input \'size\' in the first text box and
		\'winkers\' in second, which represents the unit (we
		T-winkers measure the size of our winks that way).
		\n\nSo when I
		do my tiddly-winks set I will input a number
		representing the progessively larger sizes. That
		way this program can properly track my tiddly-wink
		size progress. Sweet.</string>
	<string name="addexer_other_desc_title">Describe a Measurement</string>
	<string name="addexer_other_desc_msg">Type in this box the measurement that you will do for this new exercise. For my tiddly-winks workout, I put \'winks\' in this box.</string>

	<string name="addexer_radio_help_title">Significant Measurement</string>
	<string name="addexer_radio_help_msg">There is always one
		part of a workout that is more important than the
		others.
		\n\nTouch the radio button to the right of
		that measurement to tell the program which part you think
		is the most important. For example, squats are all about
		the weight. So make sure the \'weighted\' line has its
		radio button turned on. For jogging, the \'distanced\'
		line is probably what you are most interested in.</string>

	<string name="addexer_done_title">Done</string>
	<string name="addexer_done_msg">When you\'re satisfied with all the details of this exercise, press this button (\'done\'), and this will be added to your list of exercies.</string>

	<string name="addexer_cancel_title">Cancel Add</string>
	<string name="addexer_cancel_msg">If you decide to not add this
		exercise, hit the \'cancel\' button. The program will forget
		this entire entry.</string>

	<string name="addexer_ok_title">Okay Button</string>
	<string name="addexer_ok_msg">Tap on this button
		when you are satisfied and done adding this new
		exercise. Duh.</string>


	<!-- ============	  ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Grid ============ -->
	<!-- ============	  ============ -->

	<!-- First the menu -->
	<string name="grid_title">Your Exercises</string>
	<string name="grid_select_title">select an exercise</string>

	<string name="grid_help_title">Help!</string>
	<string name="grid_help_button">help</string>
	<string name="grid_help_msg">Yeah, this screen can look
		very complicated, but it\'s really not. Here you see the main
		bit that displays all the data for all your workouts.
		Also here is where you select the specific exercise you
		want to do next.
		\n\nQuick and dirty:
		\n-To record a new set for an exercise, just
		tap on the exercise name.
		\n-To see
		details of an exercise set, tap directly on its number.
		\n-Pressing and holding
		allows you to edit or delete that entry.
		\n\n--For the *real* beginner:\n
		Workouts consist of a series
		of exercises, often done in multiple sets. On this screen,
		select an exercise to perform from the left-most column.
		Another screen will pop up
		where you will enter the details of the set. To perform
		another set, select this exercise again.
		\n\nDon\'t see the
		exercise you want to perform (or you don\'t see any
		exercises at all)\? press \"add exercise\" to enter a
		new exercise. To edit an exercise or remove it
		completely, press and hold that particular exercise.
		\n\nTo modify the order that the exercises appear, press
		the \"order\" button. You will go to a new screen to
		change the order of the exercises.
		\n\nWhen you have finally completed your workout, select
		the \"done\" button.
		\n\nWhew, that was good; time for a shower!
		</string>


	<!-- Now the buttons -->
	<string name="grid_add_button">add</string>
	<string name="grid_add_title">Add an Exercise</string>
	<string name="grid_add_msg">This button takes you to a new
		screen where you can add a new exercise. It\'s pretty
		easy; try it!
		</string>

	<string name="grid_order_button">order</string>
	<string name="grid_order_title">Rearrange Exercise Order</string>
	<string name="grid_order_msg">All your exercises appear in
		the order you entered them. This ain\'t always the way
		you like it. Tap this button to go to a screen to
		modify the order to make it juuuust right.
		</string>


	<string name="grid_done_title">Done Working Out</string>
	<string name="grid_done_msg">When you have completed all
		your sets of all your exercises (as well as any cool-down
		routines) tap this button to signal you\'re done. Grab a
		smoothie, you deserve it!
		</string>


	<!-- Lastly the context menus on the exercise selections -->
	<string name="grid_select_help_title">Select Exercise</string>
	<string name="grid_select_help_msg">Scroll through the
		exercise list here and tap on an exercise to start
		doing a set. To do more than one set of an exercise,
		just tap on it again.
		</string>

	<!-- The yes/no dialog about editing an exercise -->
	<string name="grid_edit_dialog_title">Edit an Exercise\?</string>
	<string name="grid_edit_dialog_msg">Are you sure you want to
		edit the exercise:
	</string>

	<!-- The seperator between the number of sets done in a
		day (of a specific exercise) and the highest significant
		aspect.
	-->
	<string name="grid_edit_seperator">\u0020\u003a\u0020</string>

	<!-- Used when there's an illegal number (-1) for the most
			significant aspect of a cell.  This can happen if the
			user modifies an exercise and changes the significant
			aspect.
		-->
	<string name="grid_cell_negative_symbol">n/a</string>


	<!-- ============      ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Edit ============ -->
	<!-- ============      ============ -->
	<!-- Note:  Since this is so similar to the Add screen lots
		of strings can be found there. -->

	<string name="editexer_help_title">Edit Exercise Help</string>
	<string name="editexer_help_msg">This screen gives you the
		ability to modify or delete an exercise. And here begins
		a very long help message:
		\n\nWARNING:\n
		\tChanging an exercise may have odd results
		on workout sets that you have already done with this
		exercise.
		\n\nI\'ll do my best to try to retain data, but
		some things just won\'t work (like changing the
		unit--there is no way I can convert from the old
		unit to the new one without forcing you to enter
		some sort of formula, which is the sort of thing
		you\'re avoiding by using a computer, right?).
		\n\nConsequently, the sets you did before the change
		may be messed up. But you can edit them and fix
		the weirdness if you like.
		\n\nTo start, the textbox near the top allows you to change the
		name if you don\'t like it.
		\n\nExercises generally fall into two different types: anaerobic
		and aerobic. Anaerobic are strength building exercises like
		bench presses and squats. Aerobic exercises build endurance
		and cardiovascular health (jogging, jump rope, and swimming
		for examples). You need to tell this program what type of
		exercise this is because it does keep track, and we don\'t
		want to confuse how your muscles are worked!
		\n\nAlso, this program wants to know which group of muscles
		you are using with this exercise. You don\'t have to be
		too specific; a rough guesstimate is good enough.
		\n\nSelect the
		checkbox to left for each measurement you want to record
		for this exercise. Uncheck to disable this measurement.
		\n\nThen touch the drop-down to the right to select the unit
		of measurement.  If you want to create your own unit,
		select \'customize\' and fill in the following form.
		\n\nFor each exercise, there is usually one measurement that
		is the most important. Select the radio button on the right
		side next to the measurement that is the most important
		part of this particular exercise.
		\n\nThe \'other\' section allows you to completely customize.
		You can name both the measurement AND the unit. This is
		for those exercises that I just could not think of.
		\n\nAnd like always, you can long-touch (touch and hold for
		two seconds) any widget and get specific help for that
		item.
		\n\nNow for an example:\n
		My buddy is a tiddly-winks champion and does a very specific
		exercise to train for this sport called winking.
		\n\nSo he enters \'winking\' for the name.
		\n\nHe always count repetitions, so he checks \'reps\'.
		\n\nThere are no levels to this exercise, so he leaves this
		unchecked (levels are generally used with exercise machines
		like Stair Steppers or rowers).
		\n\nCounting calories? for tiddly-winks? You gotta be kidding!
		\n\nWinks do have a weight, so he checks \'weighted\'.
		He then presses on the drop-down nextdoor and select \'grains\',
		the unit of weight for a wink.
		\n\nWhen winking, they do go a distance, but that is not important
		(accuracy is), so he leaves this unchecked.
		\n\nTime is not an issue in this sport, so that also remains
		unchecked.
		\n\nBut there is one more aspect to the tiddly-winks workout that
		the program has not provided for: accuracy. So my friend
		checks \'other\' and types \'accuracy\' in the textbox
		next to it.
		\n\nThe unit for accuracy while winking is \'tiddles\', so
		he types this in the lower box.
		\n\nLastly, he must decide which of these is the most significant
		part of the winking exercise. While accuracy is important, this
		is an exercise, and he wants to keep track of the repetitions.
		So he selects the right-most radio button in the \'reps\' row.
		\n\nLike other programs you have used, hit \'ok\' to save the
		changes, and \'cancel\' if you change your mind and like
		things the way they were.
		\n\nRemember, if you later decide to change anything, then come
		back to the Edit Excercise screen any time.
		\n\nThat\'s it.  Sorry for the long explanation, but I think it\'s
		better to bore you than to let you languish in confusion. Have
		a great workout!
	</string>


	<!-- The Widgets -->

	<!-- For the title at the top of the screen. -->
	<string name="editexer_title_edit_msg">Edit Exercise</string>

	<!-- The TextView label preceeds name edittext widget. -->
	<string name="editexer_name_label">name</string>

	<!-- These are for the AlertDialog that comes up as a ContextMenu -->
	<string name="editexer_name_help_title">Exercise Name</string>
	<string name="editexer_name_help_msg">Type in the name of
		this exercise here.</string>

	<string name="editexer_cancel_title">Cancel Button</string>
		<string name="editexer_cancel_msg">If you decide to not
		edit this exercise, hit the \'cancel\' button. The
		program will forget this whole sordid episode.</string>

	<string name="editexer_cancel_warning_title">Cancel Exercise</string>
	<string name="editexer_cancel_warning_msg">I think you have made
		some changes to this exercise.
		\n\nAre you sure you want to cancel these changes\?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>

	<string name="editexer_ok_butt">execute changes</string>
	<string name="editexer_ok_title">Okay Button</string>
	<string name="editexer_ok_msg">Tap on this button
		when you are satisfied and done editing this
		exercise. Yep, that\'ll do it.</string>

	<string name="editexer_delete_button">delete exercise</string>
	<string name="editexer_delete_help_title">Delete Exercise</string>
	<string name="editexer_delete_help_msg">Yep, this button does
		exactly what you think it does:
		\nIt completely removes this particular exercise from the app.
		\n\nAlso note that any earlier workout sets that you
		recorded with this exercise will be deleted, too. So
		think a bit before hitting this button.
		\n\nAnd since this IS kind of a big deal, a confirmation
		dialog will pop up. It\'s the least I could do.
	</string>
	<string name="editexer_delete_confirm_title">Delete \'%s\'\?</string>
	<string name="editexer_delete_confirm_msg">Hey you! Pay
		attention!
		\n\nYou are about to completely remove the \"%s\" exercise from
		this program. That means that all data using this
		exercise will be lost.
		\n\nIf you are thinking, \"Of course, that is exactly what I
		want,\" then press \'yes\'.
		\n\nOtherwise, I think you will want to tap \'no\'
		(or hit the \'back\' button).
		</string>

	<!-- Error Messages -->
	<string name="editexer_warning_no_name">Please enter a name for this exercise!</string>
	<string name="editexer_dup_name_msg">That name is already used!</string>
	<string name="editexer_warning_no_checked">Please check a measurement for this exercise!</string>
	<string name="editexer_warning_no_significant">Please select a radio button
		to indicate most important.</string>
	<string name="editexer_warning_no_weight_unit">Hey, I need a weight unit!</string>
	<string name="editexer_warning_no_dist_unit">Uh, what about a measurement of distance\?</string>
		<string name="editexer_warning_no_time_unit">You forgot to tell me what unit of time (seconds, minutes, hours, etc.)</string>


	<!-- ============               ============ -->
	<!-- ============ AddWeightItem ============ -->
	<!-- ============               ============ -->
	<string name="add_weight_item_help_title">Adding a Custom Weight</string>
	<string name="add_weight_item_help_msg">This page allows
		you to customize the weight unit for this exercise. I don\'t
		know how strong you are or what exercises you\'re doing,
		so I can\'t always predict the units of measurement you
		may need.  This is where you tell me what you\'re lifting.
		\n\nFor example, let\'s say that I\'m aspiring to be an Olympic
		rocket skater (just use your imagination). And I need to
		be able to lift my feet while wearing my skates a certain number of rocket skate
		units. And those units are named after the first rocket skater,
		Timothy Grosserbaumbergotten von Schloffenman Rodriguez di
		Gamba.
		\n\nJust type it in. The program will remember.  And of course,
		you can always come back and change things to TGvSRdG. I won\'t
		tell.</string>

	<string name="add_weight_item_et_help_title">Custom Weight Here</string>
	<string name="add_weight_item_et_help_msg">This is a widget to
		hold text. The text to put in should be some sort of weight
		measurement....I know, something related to your workout! Yeah,
		that\'s it: some sort of weight measurement for THIS exercise
		that you\'re working on right now!
		\n\nHere\'s a gold star!</string>

	<string name="add_weight_item_prompt">What unit of weight for this
		exercise\?</string>

	<!-- ============             ============ -->
	<!-- ============ AddDistItem =========== -->
	<!-- ============             ============ -->
		<string name="add_dist_item_help_title">Adding a Custom Distance</string>
	<string name="add_dist_item_help_msg">This page allows
		you to customize the distance unit for this exercise. I don\'t
		dare guess what distance would be reasonable for this exercise,
		so you will have to tell me how far you\'re going or moving.
		\n\nLet\'s use the rocket skater example again. These people go really far,
		but to get better ratings, the television producers decided to
		avoid the nerdy astronomer units and adopt the more amusing unit of
		flatumeters.
		\n\nSo just type in flatumeters. The program will remember.  You can
		even come back later and type in much ruder units. The program won\'t
		even flinch.
		</string>

	<string name="add_dist_item_et_help_title">Custom Distance Here</string>
	<string name="add_dist_item_et_help_msg">This is a widget to
		hold the text of some sort of distance
		measurement. I wasn\'t omniscient enough
		to predict how you want to measure the distance for this
		exercise. Sorry.
		</string>

	<string name="add_dist_item_prompt">What unit of distance for this
		exercise\?</string>


	<!-- ============             ============ -->
	<!-- ============ AddTimeItem ============ -->
		<!-- ============             ============ -->
		<string name="add_time_item_help_title">Adding a Custom Time Unit</string>
	<string name="add_time_item_help_msg">Time is always slipping... :)
		and this page allows you to get a litte better grip on it
		by using whatever time unit you want for this exercise.
		\n\nBack to the rocket skater: For the sprints, the time units are
		very tiny. Oh yeah, these things are FAST for short distances.
		So we like to use microseconds.
		\n\nBut, uh, ... I didn\'t put microseconds in my list! No sweat
		(hehe), type
		it in and we\'re back in business.
		</string>

	<string name="add_time_item_et_help_title">Custom Time Here</string>
	<string name="add_time_item_et_help_msg">This is a text area to
		type in your favorite unit of time for this exercise.
		\n\nSigh, not very funny this time.
		</string>

	<string name="add_time_item_prompt">What unit of time for this
		exercise\?</string>

	<!-- ============          ============ -->
	<!-- ============ AddOther ============ -->
		<!-- ============          ============ -->
		<string name="add_other_name_et_help_title">The NAME For this Measurement</string>
		<string name="add_other_name_et_help_msg" >
		Okay, this is a little esoteric,
		but if you hang on with me, I think we can get this figured out.
		\n\nIn case you come up with an exercise that has some sort
		of measurement that is NOT a repetition, level, calorie, weight,
		distance, or some sort of elapsed time, you can fill this out
		to fulfill this need.
		\n\nAs an avid rocket skater, I need to measure the volume of
		rocket fuel that I ingest because, as you
		well know, the more fuel you drink the faster you go. So
		for this particular exercise, I simply force myself to drink
		as much as I can (tasty!).
		\n\nHowever, you can see that volume is not a measurement that
		I have listed. Wouldn\'t it be nice to record and keep track
		of how much (volume) I\'m forcing down my throat\?
		\n\nThis space is where you name
		that measurement. I am going to type in \"volume\" for this entry,
		which is the name of the measurement. The actual unit will
		go in the next textbox.
		\n\nYeah, that\'s as clear as mud. Sorry, I\'m doing
		my best; I\'m a programmer, not a writer.
		</string>

		<string name="add_other_unit_et_help_title">The UNIT For this Measurement</string>
	<string name="add_other_unit_et_help_msg">Continuing from the help on
		the previous textbox (\"other Name\"), we still need to record
		the unit of volume for this exercise.
		\n\nYes, we rocket skaters are an odd group, and when we drink we
		REALLY drink. Since rocket fuel is measured in liters, that
		would be a good way to measure our drinking.
		\n\nBut since we feed our head with this foamy redish brown fuel,
		rocket skaters prefer the word \'redhead\' over liters.
		\n\nSo I would simply type \"redheads\" in this textbox.
		\n\nAnd every
		time I do this exercise, it will ask me, \"How many redheads
		did you do in this set\?\"  And I will grin quietly.
	</string>

	<!-- ============          ============ -->
	<!-- ============ EditRows ============ -->
		<!-- ============          ============ -->
	<string name="row_edit_title">Edit Rows</string>
	<string name="row_edit_desc">Tap the arrows to move a row up or
		down.</string>

	<string name="row_edit_help_title">Help Edit Rows</string>
	<string name="row_edit_help_msg">This screen lets you change
		the order of the exercises.
		\n\nIt\'s pretty simple: just click the up or down arrows
		next to the exercise you want to move.  Try it, you\'ll
		like it!
		\n\nAnd as usual, you can cancel if you don\'t like your
		changes.
	</string>

	<string name="row_edit_cancel_warning_title">Cancel Row Change</string>
	<string name="row_edit_cancel_warning_msg">I think you have made
		some changes to the row order here.
		\n\nAre you sure you want to cancel these changes\?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>

	<!-- ============      ============ -->
	<!-- ============ ASet ============ -->
		<!-- ============      ============ -->

	<string name="aset_title">Do a Set!</string>

		<string name="aset_enter_butt">enter set</string>
		<string name="aset_entered_msg">Entered!</string>

		<string name="aset_help_title">Enter a Set Help</string>
	<string name="aset_help_msg">You\'re now working hard,
		executing a rigorous set of an arduous exercise.
		Tell us about it, that\'s what this program is for,
		right\?

		\n\nThe data from the last time you did the set is
		automatically filled in. You can change them or
		press the \'clear\' button and start fresh. (Your
		stress condition is ALWAYS set to \'ok\' and the
		notes from your previous set is just a hint--it will
		disappear when you save or start writing something else.)

		\n\nInput the numbers and any comments and don\'t forget
		to press
		\'enter set\'! That\'s how this program knows to enter
		this information into the database.

		\n\nSelect a radio button that indicates how hard this
		set has been for you (I call it the \'stress\' level).
		If the workout was too easy or you\'re ready to
		up the amps, press \'+\'. If this set was so hard
		that you could not finish, tap \'-\'. If something
		odd or bad happened (an injury, an interruption, etc.),
		press the \'X\'.

		\n\nAnd the notes section is there for whatever pops up.
		Try writing \"War and Peace\" while cooling down between sets!
		</string>

	<string name="aset_leave_title">Really\?</string>
	<string name="aset_leave_msg">Are you sure you want to
		go back to the main workout screen\? This will
		abandon all entries you\'ve made here.</string>

	<string name="aset_weight_label">weight (%s)</string>
	<string name="aset_weight_off_label">weight</string>
		<string name="aset_weight_help_title">Weight</string>
	<string name="aset_weight_help_msg">Enter the weight
		that you\'re using on this set.  Please note that if you change
		weights, you are really starting a new set.</string>
	<string name="aset_weight_hint">%s</string>

	<string name="aset_reps_label">reps</string>
	<string name="aset_reps_help_title">Reps</string>
	<string name="aset_reps_help_msg">Reps are short
		for \'repetitions.\' Tell the program how many
		times you did this exercise.  I can\'t believe
		I have to explain this.</string>
	<string name="aset_reps_hint">1, 2, 3...</string>

	<string name="aset_time_label">time (%s)</string>
	<string name="aset_time_off_label">time</string>
		<string name="aset_time_unit">minutes</string>
	<string name="aset_time_help_title">Time</string>
	<string name="aset_time_help_msg">Just enter the time
		you spent on this exercise. Use the units provided.
		You can change the time units by long-pressing this
		exercise in the main grid.</string>
	<string name="aset_time_hint">%s</string>

	<string name="aset_level_label">level</string>
	<string name="aset_level_help_title">Level</string>
	<string name="aset_level_help_msg">Enter the level that
		you used for this set. Levels are usually some sort
		of setting on a machine. For example, my recumbent
		bicycle exerciser has settings ranging from 0 to 300.</string>
	<string name="aset_level_hint">what level\?</string>

	<string name="aset_calorie_label">calories</string>
	<string name="aset_calorie_help_title">Calories</string>
	<string name="aset_calorie_help_msg">How many calories
		did you burn this set?
		\n\nUseless and confusing information:\n
		\tIn the science world, a calorie is the amount of
		heat necessary to raise one gram of water one degree
		Celcius.
		\n\nThis isn\'t very much, compared to the
		massive amount of heat food can produce . So in the
		world of food and exercise, people have used the
		same word differently (sometimes called a \'dietary
		calorie\'): one thousand times more heat! enough
		to raise a kilogram of water one degree Celsius.
		\n\nImagine if we were using the small scientific
		calorie: \"Hey, George!  You\'re gonna have to
		jog a long time to match the 300,000 calories from that
		candy bar!\"
		</string>
	<string name="aset_calorie_hint">how many calories\?</string>

		<string name="aset_distance_label">distance (%s)</string>
	<string name="aset_distance_off_label">distance</string>
		<string name="aset_distance_help_title">Distance Unit</string>
	<string name="aset_distance_help_msg">Enter the distance
		that you covered with this set. Decimal points are
		icky, so just round to the closest or change units
		(a mile is 5280 feet!).</string>
	<string name="aset_distance_hint">%s</string>

	<string name="aset_other_label_old">%1$s (%2$s)</string>
	<string name="aset_other_label">%s</string>
		<string name="aset_other_off_label">other</string>
		<string name="aset_other_help_title">Other</string>
	<string name="aset_other_help_msg">While doing your
		%1$s exercise, enter the number of %2$s here. Hope that
		sentence makes sense.
		</string>
	<string name="aset_other_hint">%s</string>

	<string name="aset_cond_label">stress</string>
	<string name="aset_cond_stress_ok">ok</string>
	<string name="aset_cond_stress_too_hard">-</string>
		<string name="aset_cond_stress_too_easy">+</string>
		<string name="aset_cond_stress_injury">X</string>
		<string name="aset_cond_stress_error">error!</string>
		<string name="aset_cond_stress_none">n/a</string>

		<string name="aset_cond_help_title">Set Stress</string>
	<string name="aset_cond_help_msg">This is a quick way
		to rate the the stress-levels when you do a set.
		I just leave it blank for
		a decent set. Select a plus-sign (\+) if you need
		to move up a notch next time. I use a minus (-) if
		I could not complete the set. And select an \'X\'
		if you injured yourself--ouch!</string>

	<string name="aset_notes_label">notes</string>
	<string name="aset_notes_help_title">Notes</string>
	<string name="aset_notes_help_msg">If you have anything
		to add to this set, jot it down here. It\'s great
		place to jot down phone numbers--what other app
		thinks this far ahead\?.</string>
	<string name="aset_notes_hint">anything at all...</string>

	<string name="aset_cancel_warning_title">Cancel Workout Set</string>
	<string name="aset_cancel_warning_msg">You\'ve started
		filling in the details for this set.  Are you sure
		you want to cancel\?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>

	<string name="aset_cancel_help_title">Cancel Help</string>
	<string name="aset_cancel_help_msg">Tap this button
		to forget about this set and go back to
		the main exercise grid.

		\n\nSurprised?  I didn\'t think so.</string>

	<string name="aset_enter_help_title">Enter Help</string>
	<string name="aset_enter_help_msg">
		Clicking on this button tells the app that you are
		done entering data for this set.

		\n\nThis adds the details of this exercise set to
		that great big database you are making with all
		these workouts.

		\n\nWhew, wipe off that sweat and take 30 sec
		to catch your breath. YEAH!
	</string>

	<string name="aset_nag_title">Save With Blank Fields\?</string>
	<string name="aset_nag_msg_plural">I think you may have forgotten
		to fill out these fields:\n
		%s
		\n
		This is not really a
		problem, but now is your a chance to go back and fill them in.
		\n\nShall I go ahead and save, leaving some blanks?</string>
	<string name="aset_nag_msg_singular">Looks like you forgot
		to fill in the %1$s field.
		\n\nThis is not really a problem, but now is your chance to
		go back and fill it in.
		\n\nShall I go ahead and save, leaving a blank?</string>

	<string name="aset_nag_significant_title">Blank Field!</string>
	<string name="aset_nag_significant_msg">You left the %1$s
		field blank!
		\n\nBlank fields are generally not a problem. But since you
		marked \'%2$s\' as the significant aspect of the %3$s exercise,
		I have to insist that you put something there. Please?</string>

	<string name="aset_nag_enter_empty_title">Enter on Empty</string>
	<string name="aset_nag_enter_empty_msg">You clicked on \'enter set\',
		but didn\'t do anything!
		\n\nSorry, but you gotta give me at least one number to enter.
	</string>

	<string name="aset_nag_no_changes_title">Enter Without Changes</string>
	<string name="aset_nag_no_changes_msg">It looks like you didn\'t
		make any changes.  Are you sure that you want
		to enter this set?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
		</string>

	<string name="aset_clear_button">clear</string>
	<string name="aset_clear_button_help_title">Clear Help</string>
	<string name="aset_clear_button_help_msg">
		This button is pretty straight-forward; it simply clears
		all the entries in this workout set.
	</string>

	<string name="aset_radio_help_title">Stress Help</string>
	<string name="aset_radio_help_msg">
		These four radio buttons are provided to give an
		indication of how stressful this particular workout
		set is to accomplish.

		\n\nThe default is \'ok\'. This indicates that this
		set was a good difficulty level. Most of the time
		the sets will be this level (I hope!), so this is
		the default.

		\n\nThe plus sign, \'+\', indicates that this set
		was too easy, and you are ready to increase the
		difficulty for your next set.

		\n\nWhat\'s the opposite of plus? minus of course!
		The \'-\' sign indicates that this set was too hard.
			You could not finish the set. Seriously consider
			making your next set easier.

			\n\nThe \'X\' is bad, very bad. Sometimes we are
			too zealous with our workouts and get hurt. Mark these with the
			big nasty \'X\'. You may want to make a note about
			how and why this happened so you don\'t repeat this
			problem again.
	</string>


	<!-- ============           ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Inspector	============ -->
	<!-- ============           ============ -->

	<string name="inspector_title">Set Inspector</string>
	<string name="inspector_empty">No Sets to Display</string>

	<string name="inspector_another_set_button">do another</string>
	<string name="inspector_another_help_title">Do Another Set</string>
	<string name="inspector_another_help_msg">
		Like the exercise that you see? Want to do it again?
		Well, my friend, this button is for you!
		\n\nPress the \"do another\" button to...yes, you guessed
		it, do another set of this exercise! Weeeee, isn\'t
		working out fun?
	</string>

	<string name="inspector_back_title">Go Back Help</string>
	<string name="inspector_back_msg">
		Really? You\'re tired of looking at this information
		and want do go back to the previous screen?  REALLY?
		\n\nI don\'t blame you a bit. You probably have more
		important things to do than look at my carefully
		crafted user interface.  Go ahead--you won\'t
		hurt my feelings.  Sigh.
	</string>

	<string name="inspector_description_plural">Here are the %1$s %2$s sets
		that you did on %3$s:</string>
	<string name="inspector_description_singular">Here is the
		%1$s set you did on %2$s:</string>

	<string name="inspector_set_title">Set #%d</string>

	<string name="inspector_set_day_label">Day Label</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_reps_label">reps</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_weight_label">weight (%s)</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_level_label">level</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_calories_label">calories</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_dist_label">distance (%s)</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_time_label">time (%s)</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_other_label">%1$s (%2$s)</string>

	<string name="inspector_null_value">null</string>
	<string name="inspector_skipped_value">skipped</string>

	<string name="inspector_set_stress_label">stress level</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_notes_label">notes</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_notes_data_none">no comment</string>

	<string name="inspector_help_title">Inspector Help</string>
	<string name="inspector_help_msg">
		This screen allows you to inspect and modify specific
		exercise sets,
		with the most recent at the top.
		\n\nLong click on an exercise set to edit (or even delete)
		details of that set. This way
		you can go back
		and fix mistakes or even erase bad memories. After all,
		we\'re only human.
	</string>
	<string name="inspector_set_time_error">no time specified</string>

	<!-- ============         ============ -->
	<!-- ============ EditSet ============ -->
		<!-- ============         ============ -->

	<string name="editset_title">Edit a Set</string>
	<string name="editset_msg">Tap to change.</string>
	<string name="editset_date_day_label">date</string>
	<string name="editset_date_time_label">time</string>
	<string name="editset_reps_label">reps</string>
	<string name="editset_weight_label">weight (%s)</string>
	<string name="editset_level_label">level</string>
	<string name="editset_cals_label">calories</string>
	<string name="editset_dist_label">distance (%s)</string>
	<string name="editset_time_label">time (%s)</string>
	<string name="editset_other_label">%1$s (%2$s)</string>
	<string name="editset_stress_label">stress level</string>
	<string name="editset_notes_label">notes</string>

	<string name="editset_empty_data">no data</string>
	<string name="editset_empty_notes">no comment</string>
	<string name="editset_notes_hint">type notes here</string>
	<string name="editset_delete_button">delete set</string>

	<string name="editset_cancel_warning_title">Cancel Edit</string>
	<string name="editset_cancel_warning_msg">I think you have made
		some changes to this exercise set.
		\n\nAre you sure you want to cancel these changes\?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>

	<string name="editset_help_title">Edit Exercise Set</string>
	<string name="editset_help_msg">
		This screen allows you to modify or delete an exercise
		set that you have already entered.
		\n\nTap on the data that you want to change. A dialog
		will pop up where you can enter a new value.
		\n\nPress the \'delete set\' button to remove the
		whole set. Beware, because you can\'t get it back
		(other than entering it in again).
		\n\nAs usual, if you change your mind, you can hit
		the \'back\' or the \'cancel\' buttons.
	</string>

	<string name="editset_delete_warning_title">Delete a Set</string>
	<string name="editset_delete_warning_msg">
		You are about to delete a set of the %1$s exercise. There
		is no going back (other than re-entering it).
		\n\nAre you sure you want to delete the %2$s set performed
		on %3$s at %4$s?
	</string>

	<!-- ============                ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Enter a Number ============ -->
		<!-- ============                ============ -->

	<string name="enter_a_number_default_title">NO TITLE</string>
	<string name="enter_a_number_old_value">Type in a new
		value
		\n(originally: %s)</string>

	<string name="enter_a_number_help_title">Number Help</string>
	<string name="enter_a_number_help_msg">
		Type in a number here.
		\n\n\n\nGee, why do I even bother? \'Cause I\'m anal, that\'s
		why.
		\n\nI... must... cross... the... T\'s... dot...
		the... I\'s... and... ... ...
		\n\n
		...breathe! Whew.
	</string>

	<string name="enter_a_number_cancel_warn_title">Cancel Number Change</string>
	<string name="enter_a_number_cancel_warn_msg">
		It looks like you made some changes to this number.
		\n\nAre you sure you want to cancel these changes?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>

	<!-- ============            ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Enter Text ============ -->
		<!-- ============            ============ -->
	<string name="enter_text_default_title">Change Note</string>
	<string name="enter_text_msg_empty">Type in a note
		for this set:</string>
	<string name="enter_text_msg_old">Type in the new
		note.  Here\'s the old one to compare with:
		</string>

	<string name="enter_text_help_title">Note Help</string>
	<string name="enter_text_help_msg">
		Yep. You type right here. Yesiree, that\'ll do it.
		Anything you like. Type it. However your phone or
		device does it. Do it here.
		\n\nThat\'s a good boy (or girl or whatever).
	</string>

	<string name="enter_text_cancel_warn_title">Cancel Note Change</string>
	<string name="enter_text_cancel_warn_msg">
		It looks like you made some changes to your note.
		\n\nAre you sure you want to cancel these changes?
		\n\n(You can turn this warning off in the \'preferences\'.)
	</string>


	<!-- ============              ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Enter Stress ============ -->
		<!-- ============              ============ -->
	<string name="enter_stress_title">Stress Level</string>
	<string name="enter_stress_prod">Select the stress
		level for this workout set.</string>
	<string name="enter_stress_help_title">Stress Help</string>
	<string name="enter_stress_help_msg">
		Select the stress level of this exercise set.
		\n\nIn general:\n
		\t\'ok\' is for your normal workout.\n
		\t\'+\' means that this was too easy; make it hard
		next time.\n
		\t\'-\' indicates that this set was too hard; you
		either could not finish or had to strain.\n
		\t\'X\' is bad, an injury or something very unusual
		occurred.
		\n\nYou don\'t have to do these. I just find them helpful
		to know when it\'s time to up the weight or increase
		the difficulty.
	</string>

	<string name="enter_stress_cond_label">stress</string>
	<string name="enter_stress_cond_stress_ok">ok</string>
	<string name="enter_stress_cond_stress_too_hard">- (too hard)</string>
		<string name="enter_stress_cond_stress_too_easy">+ (not hard enough)</string>
		<string name="enter_stress_cond_stress_injury">X (injury)</string>
		<string name="enter_stress_cond_stress_error">error!</string>
		<string name="enter_stress_cond_stress_none">n\/a</string>


	<!-- ============              ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Preferences  ============ -->
		<!-- ============              ============ -->

		<string name="prefs_nag_key">nag</string>
		<string name="prefs_nag_title">Nagging</string>
		<string name="prefs_nagging_is_off_msg">Nagging is reduced.
			\nYou will still get messages that are *really* important!
			\n\n(I\'m sick and tired of the program asking me to fill
			out forms and fields that I don\'t have time to fool with!)
	</string>
		<string name="prefs_nagging_is_on_msg">Nagging is on.
			\n\n(I like being reminded of things that I may have
			forgotten to do.)
			</string>

		<string name="prefs_sound_key">sound</string>
		<string name="prefs_sound_title">Play Sounds</string>
	<string name="prefs_sound_on_msg">Can you hear that?
		Yeah, I think this program is trying to make some noises!</string>
	<string name="prefs_sound_off_msg">Shhhhh, we\'re playing
		the quiet game now. Don\'t make a sound.</string>

		<string name="prefs_display_key">display</string>
		<string name="prefs_display_title">Screen Saver</string>
	<string name="prefs_display_keep_on_msg">The display will
		stay on as long as this app is activie.</string>
	<string name="prefs_display_save_screen_msg">While using
		this app, the screen saver will kick in
		according to your system settings.</string>

	<!-- ============                 ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Graph Selector  ============ -->
	<!-- ============                 ============ -->

	<string name="graph_selector_title">Graphs!</string>
	<string name="graph_selector_exercise_msg">Which exercise
		do you want to look at?</string>

	<string name="graph_selector_help_title">Select a Graph</string>
	<string name="graph_selector_help_msg">
		Here is a list of all your exercises. Tap on one to see your
		progress in that exercise.
		\n\nRemember when you made the exercise, you noted one of the
		bits as significant? Well that\'s the part that will be graphed.
	</string>

	<!-- ============        ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Graph  ============ -->
	<!-- ============        ============ -->

	<string name="graph_title_msg">%s</string>

	<string name="graph_help_title">Graph Help</string>
	<string name="graph_help_msg">You want to see your progress (or
		lack thereof)? This is the place to be.
		\n\nOn this screen you see a graph (also called a chart) of
		this exercise.
		\n\nThe horizontal axis is time, with each individual
		exercise set presented with its own position.
		\n\nThe vertical lines represent the quantities of the
		significant aspect of that exercise (remember that? it\'s
		the part of the exercise with the radio button selected
		next to it when you defined this exercise).  For example,
		if you were doing bench presses and weight (\'pounds\')
		were the significant portion, then the graph shows all
		the different weights (in pounds, of course!) you did for
		all your exercise sets.
		\n\nIf you see gaps, that means that there were times
		that did not have entries for this exercise for this
		aspect.
		</string>

	<string name="graph_units_msg1">%s</string>
	<string name="graph_units_msg2">%1$s (%2$s)</string>

	<string name="graph_no_sets_msg">No data for this exercise</string>
	<string name="graph_1_set_msg">Just one set: %s</string>
	<string name="graph_illegal_sets_msg">Error trying to graph!</string>
	<string name="graph_all_same_value_msg">All sets are the same value: %s</string>
	<string name="graph_all_invalid_msg">All values are invalid, so there\'s
		nothing to graph. Sorry. Try filling some of the missing values.
		</string>

	<!-- ============          ============ -->
	<!-- ============ History  ============ -->
	<!-- ============          ============ -->

	<string name="history_title">History of %s</string>
	<string name="history_msg">A few of the more recent sets:</string>
	<string name="history_empty_msg">You have not done
		any sets of this exercise yet.</string>

	<string name="history_help_title">History Help</string>
	<string name="history_help_msg">
		Pressing this button shows the recent history of this
		exercise.
	</string>



	<!-- ============                   ============ -->
	<!-- ============ Exercise TabHost  ============ -->
	<!-- ============              	   ============ -->

		<string name="exercise_tabhost_to_grid_butt">back to grid</string>
	<string name="exer_tabhost_tab_aset">do a set</string>
	<string name="exer_tabhost_tab_edit_exercise">edit exercise</string>
	<string name="exer_tabhost_tab_inspector">inspector</string>
	<string name="exer_tabhost_tab_graph">graph</string>
	<string name="exer_tabhost_tab_history">show history</string>


</resources>
